# **Insightful Developer**

# **Justin Parrish**

Atlanta, Georgia (678) 634-4384 justinparrish7@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Entry Level Developer with experience in Front End Web Development with React, HTML, CSS, and Javascript and Full Stack Web Development with MERN Stack and React, Django and SQLite technologies. Also have more than adequate knowledge of SQL, Agile Development, Functional Programming, and Object Oriented Programming.

## **Experience**

### **Upwork**, Remote — Freelance Front End Dev

November 2019 - PRESENT

- Communicate with clients to deliver quality projects.
- Schedule check-in with clients to ensure satisfaction with the work progress.
- Developed apps with React, Express.js, Django, MongoDb and SQLite databases.

### AK Security Services, Atlanta, Ga — Security Officer

September 2018 - April 2019

- Provide security services to the client's needs.
- Secure contracts from potential clients.
- Provide additional assistance when applicable.
- Handle each altercation with the proper etiquette.

### **Projects**

#### CDIS App

Clinical Documentation Specialist App | March 2020

The CDIS App is a full stack application developed with a ReactJs front end and a Django backend using a SQLite database. The CDIS app is currently being used by employees of Emory Healthcare in order to make their daily work task more organized and structured.

#### MotorBoard

Online/Mobile Vehicle Log | October 2019

To develop MotorBoard, React, Django, and the SQLite database were primarily used. This is a web application that is a lot similar to a car's CarFax report. The difference between the two is with MotorBoard the user has total control of what is logged about his/her vehicle.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### General Assembly, Atlanta, Ga

July 2019 - October 2019

Software Engineering Immersive Student

#### Martin Luther King Jr. High School, Lithonia, Ga — HS Diploma

August 2014 - May 2018 High School Graduate

#### Languages

Bash HTML/CSS JavaScript Python SOL

#### Libraries/Frameworks

Django Express.js jQuery Mongoose Node.js React

#### **Skills**

Agile Development Api Testing Debugging Git Mac OS/Windows OOP SQL/MongoDB